Hello everyone, in this session, I will demo how to generate TK using GitHub Corvallis.
To use this feature, first, I need to have TWSFounder created for the item I need to generate TK.
In this session, I will go to Team Support. Here, I will have two options.
The first option is to create TWSFounder for an item.
And the second option is to create TWSFounder for a list of other items.
I will demo the first option first. I will choose One Item here.
Here, I will have three different types of information.
The first information is the TWSFounder.
The first is the database-batch.
The database-batch is the folder that contains the database that I have logged in TWSFounder.
The second information is the workspace-batch.
Here, I will create an empty folder.
And I will use this folder-batch to store the outputs in the TUN running process.
The third information is the item-name.
This is the name of the item that I need to create.
And I will use this folder to create the TWSFounder.
After creating all three items, I will go to Generate Environment.
After completing this step, TUN will show me an option to notify me.
At the same time, TUN Visual Studio Code.
At the same time, TUN Visual Studio Code will automatically open and stop a TWSFounder of the item I need to create.
Here, I will have a file.
I will have two files.
The first is test.cpp.
The second is test.h.
These two are here.
In addition, I can use Open Output feature to help me open the correct folder that contains the space folder of the item I want to create here.
For the second option, I will choose List Items, and I also have three main information fields.
The first is Data By Parts, the second is Works By Parts. These two fields are similar to the first option.
And there is another point, which is the third information is List Item Parts.
Then I will have an Excel file to fill in the information of Item Names and Item Parts.
I also create a test work.
Then I click on the Space folder.
Then I will take this folder and paste it on the third column.
Then I will click on Generate Environment.
After completing this work, I click on Open Output here, then I will see the
TestWorksSpaceFounder has created for each item in the item list.
After having the TestWorksSpaceFounder for the item, I need to go to TaskK, then I will
go to AiCopilot, I choose Generate TaskK by AiCopilot.
Here I have two main information sources.
The first information source is item 3, then I will go to the TestWorksSpaceFounder of an
item.
I click on Generate TaskK.
For example, this item, then I will copy the part of this file number.
Then I will input the first information source.
And the next is the database part.
Just like the previous step, I will also input the information source of the database folder.
Then I will click on the AutoDefault Object here.
During running, you can follow the information directly by clicking on the Show Execution Log here.
Then a Terminal window will appear and it will show the information as I am running.
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
We can see that the folder has 3 functions, which are listed here.
We will choose one of the 3 functions that we want to generate test case.
The next step, we will have 2 options.
The first option is to generate test case for the function we are selecting here.
And the second option is to generate test case for all the functions in this item.
To make it easier for us to observe the running process,
while generating test case, we will open Visual Studio Code and import the item's survey folder into it.
And we will demo the first option.
to generate test case for the function we are selecting here.
We will press the button to generate one source.
We will see that the generator of the test case has been sent.
We will look at the information in Visual Studio Code.
We will output and choose GitHub Cobalt Chart here.
So the information in the generator will be sent.
and the array will be solved in this terminal
After I see the notification that the test generation completed
that is, the test generation has been completed
Next, I will click on Terminal
I will build this test
Here I have 8 TKs
and all 8 TKs have passed
Next, I will see the code coverage
I will build Canada for this test
I will click on Build Canada here
and here is the code
After that, I can find the code
to build Canada
I have the code
I will click on Build Canada
After this step, you can see
that the Rosary code
is completed
I will start to build Canada
I will open the folder of the item and I will see that there is a folder called cantata
I will open the folder called cantata
I will open the folder called Tcc
I will open the folder called tunale
I will create a project in this cantata
check name, like my atom name, I will drag the canada folder, I will
and then check the new one created on the side of Tumkantata
I will click on this .cov file
and I will remove this file
Here I see that the first function
its light code lines are blue
which means that these light codes have been covered
and these red lines have not been covered
Then I will demo my second option
which is Generate TK Onshoot
Before clicking on this Generate button
I will delete the newly created TKs
and create a new one
in the first option
to avoid being duplicated for the next time
Then I will click on Generate TK Onshoot here
to create TKs for all functions in this item
Then I will go to the next section
to create another TK
and select Generate TK Onshoot
This is also a good way to create a TK
as I have already shown in the previous video
That is a TK onshoot
I am going to create a TK onshoot
I am going to remove this TK
and select Generate TK Onshoot
I will click on the next option
I will go back to the previous section
and click on the next option
This is the first option
I will click on this and then I will go back to the previous option
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
After we finish the 3 functions, we will build the data
At this step, we can start to build the data
To build the data, we can click on the tool
Or we can build the data from the Visual Studio Code
We go to Terminal, select Runtasks
And select the data
Now we input the code
We
Ok
Let see
We use the tool to connect to
We use the tool to connect to the terminal
We can see that the colors of 3 functions in this item has been covered, so the colors of these items have changed to blue.
Then we can go to Pandata, choose View, choose Report Viewer to see this report.
We can see the test report here, and the coverage has been changed here.